timeoutkl.com 2017-03-10

# Privacy policy - Time Out Kuala Lumpur

Time Out Kuala Lumpur ("TOKL") promises to serve its audience with integrity and honesty both in its published matter and online. The same is true now that we publish online. TOKL has developed this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and to disclose our information-gathering and -sharing practices for [www.timeoutkl.com](http://www.timeoutkl.com/ "Time Out Kuala Lumpur") (the "site"). By visiting the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. Our site will develop and evolve over time, and this policy may change to reflect that.

 **TOKL privacy's promise**  
We are absolutely committed to protecting your privacy. We are also committed to the following: (1) We will not pass on any individual user details unless we have your prior consent; and (2) if we don't have your consent to pass on individual user details, we will only give advertisers aggregate statistics about the number of users and their traffic patterns. However, if TOKL changes hands, TOKL reserves the right to transfer all information collected through this site to the new owner.

 **Personal information**  
TOKL does not require you to provide any personal information in order to access the site www.timeoutkl.com. However, if you choose to fill out any reader surveys, you will be asked to supply some information about yourself, including your name, address, phone number and email address. TOKL keeps track of the number of visitors to the site, the pages they visit and how long they stay. In addition, TOKL collects information from visitors who click on advertisements so that we are able to measure interest in the various areas of our site and inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their ads. TOKL also uses demographic and preference information to allow advertising banners on our site to be targeted, in the aggregate, to the readers for whom they are most pertinent.

We collect these kinds of aggregate user information for two main reasons: (1) to help us continually improve the service we offer; and (2) to sell sponsorships on the site to appropriate advertisers. TOKL discloses this information to advertisers. Note that advertisers do not have influence over the editorial content or reviews that appear on the site.

 **Cookies and Time Out**  
Time Out's main site at www.timeout.com and our other sites such as www.timeoutkl.com use cookies to track your usage on our site. This ensures that you are a subscriber, and allows you to roam freely within our subscriber-based site without typing in a password to access each page. We do not track any of your activity as it relates to your individual movements throughout our site, only as an aggregate of data in conjunction with users to our site as a whole. Your movement is not tracked once you leave our site. Our Web site uses ad servers to serve the advertisements that you see on pages of our Web site. That partner uses cookies to help target ads to you. To find out more about the use of cookies and the information-gathering practices and opt-out procedures of AdLINK, please click here.

 **TOKL email policy**  
When you give us your email address, you are also asked to let us know how we can use it: You can opt to allow us to email you regarding your subscription, or to allow us to send you additional information via email that we believe will be of interest to you. Such requests will be opt-in only, so that you do not inadvertently agree to receive mailings you do not want.

If you participate in an online survey, you may receive a one-time mailing to confirm your transaction or interaction with our site. Such mailings are one-time only. When you give us your email address under these circumstances, you will also see a box that, when checked by you, will enable TOKL to contact you via email regarding special events, discounts and offers. If you don't want your information to be used for any of these purposes, you should not check the box.

If we ever request that you volunteer additional information, such as financial data or age (in an online survey, for example) your response will always be voluntary. In addition, there will always be a box for you to check if you choose to enable us to disclose such information to a third party.

Users may opt to receive a regular email newsletter that contains information we believe to be of value to our users, specifically special discounts and offers selected by our marketing department.

 **TOKL competitions**  
The only exception to this rule is when holding a competition we may sometimes share your email address with the company who have provided the prizes. We always ask them to ensure that you can opt out of their communications.

 **Third-party disclosure of personal information**  
Links to other sites: Our site contains links to other sites that are not under our control, even though some of them may feature the TOKL logo through a marketing agreement with us. TOKL cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of other companies. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site you visit on the Internet. TOKL may receive a commission from.

On occasion, TOKL sponsors special promotions, sweepstakes and contests that are hosted by partner websites, which may require that your browseraccept cookies.

Required disclosures: TOKL cooperates with all law-enforcement inquiries and reserves the right to disclose personally identifying or aggregate information in connection with a subpoena or other court-sanctioned demand for such information.

 **Security**  
TOKL has invested, and will continue to invest, in the best-quality security available to guard access to information, data quality, and physical security of servers where information is stored. Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Despite these efforts, we can't guarantee that a hacker will not obtain access to communications between you and the site.

 **Collection of personal data from children**  
Our site is not directed to users under the age of 16. TOKL will not knowingly (i) collect information from individuals under the age of 13 ("children") or (ii) provide any personally identifying information collected from children, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. No information collected through the site from users self-identified as children will knowingly be used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside TOKL.

 **TOKL's right to change privacy policy and no impediment on transfer of assets**  
This policy is effective as of February 2008. TOKL may change this policy at any time. You should periodically revisit our privacy policy to be sure that you are familiar with our current policy. Your use of the site following any modifications to the privacy policy will be conclusively deemed acceptance of the terms of this privacy policy and any changes to the policy. Nothing in this privacy policy is meant to impede TOKL's right or ability to transfer, sell or otherwise dispose of any of its assets.  
 **  
Personal Data Protection Act 2010**  
a) All information received is for the use of Mongoose Publishing Sdn Bhd  
b) Subscriber / Purchaser allows Mongoose Publishing Sdn Bhd to process the information received for the fulfillment of subscription / products and all processes related to the purchase  
c) Subscriber / Purchaser allows the information to be processed and passed on to a third party contractor (address details only) for fulfillment of subscription / products (delivery)  
d) Any adjustment of the subscription / purchaser's information must be in writing by the relevant party to the address stated below or emailed to subscription@mongooseasia.com

 **Mongoose Publishing Sdn Bhd (580051-K)**  
Level 36 Menara AmBank  
No 8 Jalan Yap Kwan Seng  
50450 Kuala Lumpur  
Malaysia

Tel: +6 03-2166 6650  
Fax: +6 03-2166 6651  
Web: [www.mongooseasia.com](http://www.mongooseasia.com/ "Mongoose Publishing")

### Comments
